this tutorial is about open top shapes
本教程是关于开顶形状的
有很多配置，所以
this tutorial is about open top shapes
there are a number of configurations so
这是最基础的
基于此处的平行折叠
there are a number of configurations so
this is the most the most basic it's
在这里，这个姐姐在T型链上折起来
其实只是
this is the most the most basic it's
based on a parallel fold stuck down here
一端的标签将其粘成一个循环
然后在这个下一个例子
based on a parallel fold stuck down here
and here this sister fold at the T chain
如果是同一件事，那是一条
一端带有标签的卡片
and here this sister fold at the T chain
it's really just the strip of card with
进入循环，但在这种情况下，标签
将其附加到页面上的孔
it's really just the strip of card with
a tab on one end gluing it into a loop
每边都有一个折痕
在每个角落上方，然后您需要
a tab on one end gluing it into a loop
and then stuck down next example in this
另一个折痕上方的两个折痕
基本折，所以这是一个
and then stuck down next example in this
case it's the same thing it's a strip of
类似的想法，这是一个正方形，但在
这种情况是基于v折
case it's the same thing it's a strip of
card with a tab at one end gluing it
所以是举起平行四边形的V形折叠
而我们刚刚看过的那个
card with a tab at one end gluing it
into a loop but in this case the tabs
虽然是正方形
这是基于平行折叠不
into a loop but in this case the tabs
that attach it to the page run the hole
退还这一个，这是
基于v折，但有一个折痕
that attach it to the page run the hole
of each side and then there's a crease
v停留在页面上的位置
另一端的另一个仍然只是
of each side and then there's a crease
above each corner and then you need
带有一个标签的卡环
在一起，我们会在
above each corner and then you need
another crease two creases above the
在这种情况下，我们开始呈锥形
因此对于这些，您将需要一个指南针
another crease two creases above the
base fold so that's that one this is a
画画基本图案
网，所以你可以使这种类型的
base fold so that's that one this is a
similar idea this is a square but in
像火山一样，你也可以
这种类型就像漏斗形
similar idea this is a square but in
this case this is based on a v-fold
这很容易变成
花，所以这里有一个例子
this case this is based on a v-fold
so it's a v-fold lifting a parallelogram
花艺设计，所以我们有两层
花瓣，然后我们有一个金字塔
so it's a v-fold lifting a parallelogram
whereas this one we just looked at
金字塔设计的中间
在教程21中解释所有
whereas this one we just looked at
although it's square
飞机实际上有六架飞机
被提升，所以您可以添加到
this one is based on parallel folds not
其中任何一个还有沟壑
在胶粘到的地方创建
this one is based on parallel folds not
refunds this one this again this is
将此页面粘在平行折页上
这样有两个黏住的地方
refunds this one this again this is
based on v folds but there's one crease
平行于脊椎，所以它们在哪里
胶合你创造一个沟壑，你
based on v folds but there's one crease
where the v sticks to the page and
可以内置，所以这是另一个例子
这是带有金字塔的基本花
where the v sticks to the page and
another at the other end is still just a
在中间键入机制，然后
这是一个反折的零件装入
another at the other end is still just a
loop of card with one tab holding it
沟渠
所以当你打开而不只是一个
loop of card with one tab holding it
together then we get more interesting in
像这样的直件，我们有一个
在三个维度上举起的那一块
together then we get more interesting in
this case we start getting tapered shape
所以我们只是做一个非常基础的开顶
形状只是一个粘在一起的环，所以
this case we start getting tapered shape
so for these you will need a compass to
拿一张底纸用你的底纸
所以就给自己剪一条卡
so for these you will need a compass to
draw the draw the basic pattern
好久了
将文件夹胶合片一端折叠
draw the draw the basic pattern
the net so you can make this type the
好了，现在你带另一端
你可以把它粘在胶上
the net so you can make this type the
like a volcano shape you can also make
闭上你可能想要它下面
无论如何，胶水并不重要
like a volcano shape you can also make
this type it's like a funnel shape and
这样我们就将其粘贴到一个循环中，
然后把它压扁，因为你会
this type it's like a funnel shape and
this lends itself to being turned into
需要一个你需要像这样
所以会像这个文件夹一样打开
this lends itself to being turned into
flowers so here we have an example of a
将您知道的文件标签粘贴到
一路走到尽头
flowers so here we have an example of a
flower design so we've got two layers of
双方，你只是一个很大的长折痕
把它折起来，现在你
flower design so we've got two layers of
petals and then we've got a pyramid in
只想在中间留下一个标签
两侧，所以你可以沿着
petals and then we've got a pyramid in
the middle that the pyramid design will
折痕
然后在中间留下一个部分
the middle that the pyramid design will
explain in tutorial 21 all that the
仅用于一点粘合
所以这是两个循环
explain in tutorial 21 all that the
planes there are actually six planes
标签上的标签，确保它们工作正常
带你的基地，看看你为什么想要
planes there are actually six planes
that are lifted so you can add pieces to
它看着你想要什么样的摇动
你只想要一个长椭圆形或做
that are lifted so you can add pieces to
any of those there's also gullies
你想要它几乎圆到看到多远
远离基地，你想知道我们是否去
any of those there's also gullies
created where where it's glued to the
相当圆，这就是重点
标记从脊柱一侧躺下
created where where it's glued to the
page this is glued down parallel folds
将胶水放在一个标签上，然后
将折痕粘在线上
page this is glued down parallel folds
so that there's two sticking places
平行于中央沟
将其他标签向下折平放上胶水
so that there's two sticking places
parallel to the spine and so where they
一折的底座再次关闭了
这需要很大的压力，所以
parallel to the spine and so where they
glue down you create a gully that you
确保您有机会
胶水脱落，在那里你会
glue down you create a gully that you
can build into so here's another example
只要找到相当的磨损
墙壁很短，很好，但是
can build into so here's another example
this is a basic flower with a pyramid
你走得越高，他们往往会倾向于
倾斜卡的弯曲开始
this is a basic flower with a pyramid
type mechanism in the middle and then
影响形状我现在将制作一个
花型设计，使它呈锥形
type mechanism in the middle and then
this is a counter folded piece load into
形状，因此您需要
您的指南针，所以从基础表开始
this is a counter folded piece load into
the gully
折成两折折得很好
它重新回到自身，再次折起
the gully
so as you open rather than just being a
现在拿一张卡，走吧
换一个黄色的，把指南针放在上面
so as you open rather than just being a
straight piece like this one we've got a
一侧，你需要画大一点
尽可能以弧线的方式工作
straight piece like this one we've got a
piece that lifts up three dimensionally
弧形的平面越多
花瓣会站起来
so we just make a really basic open top
方舟越紧，他们越会
躺下，如果你拿一个
so we just make a really basic open top
shapes just a loop glued together so
圈成六圈
相等的部分将是
shapes just a loop glued together so
take a base sheet use your base sheets
像这样的东西我们只是做了
实际上是完全扁平化的
take a base sheet use your base sheets
so just cut yourself a strip of card
艺术就是力量，所以现在我们
尽我们所能
so just cut yourself a strip of card
right long
所以用这个罗盘是最宽的
它会打开，所以做一个大弧线，然后
folder gluing tab onto one end fold it
决定你要花瓣多高
因此，我只是将其随机移动
folder gluing tab onto one end fold it
well now you bring the other end round
并绘制另一个RMS，然后
标记中心点
well now you bring the other end round
and you can just glue that on glue it
指南针很重要，所以
有，现在改变直径
and you can just glue that on glue it
shut you might want it underneath
改变铅笔尖之间的距离
而你不希望的是
shut you might want it underneath
doesn't really matter anyway glue on
一样的半径
这弧是所以我要去做什么
doesn't really matter anyway glue on
that so we glue that into a loop and
儿子大约四四厘米，
只是从一开始就开始测量
that so we glue that into a loop and
then you crush it flat because you will
只是测量出六个部分
做六件事真的很重要
then you crush it flat because you will
need a that you need it to be like this
一二三四五
六行，现在您需要计分
need a that you need it to be like this
so this will open up like this folder a
实现我正在使用biro，而您
从中心点划线
so this will open up like this folder a
gluing you know file tabs on to the
你的指南针点放在
用指南针标记你的所作所为
gluing you know file tabs on to the
bottom of it so all the way along one
在两个之间得分
平行弧
bottom of it so all the way along one
sides you just make a big long crease
好的，现在您将需要在
里面会将其粘贴到页面上
sides you just make a big long crease
fold it back on itself and now you you
在两个之间划一条线，然后这个
你这件事很重要
fold it back on itself and now you you
just want a tab left in the middle of
要坚持到页面，然后你
留下两个空白，然后得分
just want a tab left in the middle of
each side so you can just cut along that
在另一行
另一个标签，最后不要忘记
each side so you can just cut along that
crease
最终选项卡将要拉的选项卡
整个事情变成一个需要的循环
crease
and just leave a section in the middle
在一端我要做的标记
在这一点上，我可以看到
and just leave a section in the middle
just for a little gluing tab
指导，这是时候，如果你想
你的花瓣要成形，这就是你的
so here it is this is the loop with two
机会，是否想要他们
尖圆的你知道更多
so here it is this is the loop with two
tabs on it make sure they work nicely
有趣的是，这是要做的时刻
所以我们还是去买点东西
tabs on it make sure they work nicely
take your base see how why do you want
现在这里相当基本
所以确保你有这两个
take your base see how why do you want
it watch what sort of shakes you want
里面的标签将
粘到页面上
it watch what sort of shakes you want
you just want a long oval shape or do
好吧，这是如此冻结所有分数
花瓣之间的线将它们全部折叠
you just want a long oval shape or do
you want it nearly round to see how far
一种方式，然后回到自己
不要忘记折叠所有标签
you want it nearly round to see how far
away from the base you wonder if we go
以及这三个标签
它进入一个循环，但在这种情况下
away from the base you wonder if we go
fairly round that's the point of this
确保您将准则保持在
在下面如此旋转
fairly round that's the point of this
mark have one side lies from the spine
这样你就可以看到干净的表面
然后你把它粘起来，我们要
mark have one side lies from the spine
put glue on on just one tab and then
把它粘在后面
这就是你的基本花形
put glue on on just one tab and then
glue the the crease on that to your line
那么你需要在他们的身上排队
再次水龙头，你可以让他们去
glue the the crease on that to your line
parallel to the central gully and then
内部或外部，如果你要
使它像这样一个然后标签
parallel to the central gully and then
fold the other tab down flat put glue on
都在里面，他们都是
如果不是，所有隐藏在它下面的东西
fold the other tab down flat put glue on
that one fold the base shut this again
将要建立
您可能最好拥有标签
that one fold the base shut this again
it will take quite a lot of stress so
在外面，所以他们只是被隐藏
在花瓣的下方
it will take quite a lot of stress so
make sure you give it a chance for the
然后确保这些折痕是
在脊椎褶皱上方，然后您就可以
make sure you give it a chance for the
glue to go off and there it is you'll
胶粘到一侧，所以得到它
尽你所能
glue to go off and there it is you'll
find wear as long as it's quite the
确保这两个折痕是
中央沟上方粘住它
find wear as long as it's quite the
walls are quite short it's fine but the
现在将整个东西折叠成
平仓
walls are quite short it's fine but the
higher you go the more they will tend to
将胶水放在另一个标签上，因为
它会在你想要的外面
higher you go the more they will tend to
to lean in the bend of the card starts
该标签折回，所以是胶水
用力按以确保已胶合
to lean in the bend of the card starts
influencing the shape I'll now make a
真的很好，然后打开它
如果你想让花瓣躺下
influencing the shape I'll now make a
flower type design so that is a tapered
还需要制作初始弧线
如果需要的话，弯曲度更高，平面度更低
flower type design so that is a tapered
shape so for that yeah you will need
站起来更多，使最初的弧线
奉承这是我的一个
shape so for that yeah you will need
your compass so start with a base sheet
切割机制作的弹出卡由
多佛现在是双胞胎的一部分
your compass so start with a base sheet
folded in half crease really well fold
船的侧面有点弧形
香蕉嘘片，它粘在上面
folded in half crease really well fold
it back on itself crease it again again
每边都有这些涟漪
这些是实际上的标签
it back on itself crease it again again
now take a piece of card and let's go
将其粘贴到页面和图上
油，这是用
now take a piece of card and let's go
for a yellow one and put your compass on
系列默认
下一个是大卫蠕动的蠕虫
for a yellow one and put your compass on
one one side and you need to draw as big
佩洛姆，这里有狮子的嘴
这只是其中之一
one one side and you need to draw as big
an arc as you can the way this works
我给你看的第一批
基于V形折叠
an arc as you can the way this works
that the flat of the arc the more the
两个汇合的折痕汇合在
脊椎闭合整个脸部
that the flat of the arc the more the
petals will stand up
实际上是举升机
平行折叠的页面
petals will stand up
the tighter the ark the more they will
停留下来，那就是蠕虫
大卫·佩洛姆（David Pellom）扭动一下，接下来
the tighter the ark the more they will
lie down if you take a if you take a
马特·约翰斯顿（Matt Johnston）制作的一款弹出式桌游
这是基本的外圈
lie down if you take a if you take a
circle and just break it into six
由笔直制成的开顶形状
像第一张纸条
circle and just break it into six
sections equal sections that will be
我又给你看过这座塔
实际上是带有圆锥形的开放顶部形状
sections equal sections that will be
flat like this thing we just made that
卡在顶部但不是盒子
它曾经是一个盒子，它本来会有一个
flat like this thing we just made that
in effect was a completely flattened out
里面的盖子应该已经推出了
边缘，使整个事情有点
in effect was a completely flattened out
art it was strength and so now we're
更圆，但因为它只是一个开放
顶部的形状，你会看到它只是趋向于
art it was strength and so now we're
going as wide as we can
倾斜一点，最后一个倾斜
这是大卫·卡特（David Carter）创作的两个蓝色
going as wide as we can
so with this compass this is the widest
圆锥形火山系列以及所有
由自动剥离机操作
so with this compass this is the widest
it'll open so do a big arc and then
自动拉带是教程16和
所以这些真的是如果你正在
it'll open so do a big arc and then
decide how tall you want the petals to
一朵花，但没有花钱
在里面，所以你得到一个锥形
decide how tall you want the petals to
be so I just move it in randomly really
外面的标签，这给了
给你所有的火山形状
be so I just move it in randomly really
and draw another another RMS and then
这和更多的内容都很好地解释了
弹出式设计和纸张中的细节
and draw another another RMS and then
mark the center point where the point of
机械师
您
mark the center point where the point of
the compass is that's quite important so